Subtitles by Razed (gab.com/razed)
Gab - Speak Freely
Amman, Jordan
Let me see it.
How are you feeling?
It'll be fine. Don't be scared.
I'll kill you, you cheapskate.
Right, well, enjoy the experience.
Which experience? Death by lynching?
You know what they do to gays where they come from?
Yoni, relax. No one will touch you.
Oh, I need a selfie with one of these women in black.
What are those things called?
-Burka.
And don't mess around, Shira.
What are you talking about, it's polite to ask.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Hey!
Careful, man.
Oh my god I'm sorry.
-It hit me in the face.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-Take it easy.
Yes, yes, okay. Sorry.
-Okay.
Let me help you.
What?
I will help you.
Okay. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Excuse me.
Did you see how he got mad at me?
Rightly so.
Yes mother.
We already had tickets for Al-Al.
Yeah, at a thousand dollars.
This cost us half, it's another two months in India.
Really "Shawiya, Ya Zalma".
Like, you put the bag in front of him.
Ok fine.
I don't control you, right?
Good.
-Good.
What, you're not excited?
Excited about what?
-Excited about India.
When we get to India I'll be excited.
Good, come take a selfie.
What made the lights go off?
-No, no, it's probably an air pocket.
What air pocket?
Ladies and gentlemen, I ask all passengers to remain seated and fasten their seat belts.
Ladies and gentlemen, please fasten your seat belts. Thank you.
You're fastened?
-That's mine.
Must fasten seat belts.
Hey, okay, everything's fine.
Okay.
Did he say "Tehran?"
No, there's no way.
There's no way.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
They will arrest us, Shira, they will arrest us, don't you understand?
Israelis don't come back from Iran.
Okay honey, relax. Let's sit back down.
Everything's fine.
Put, put on your seat belt.
Does that look like Tehran to you?
I don't know.
I can't breathe, Shira.
Shhh...
Alright. Good luck.
See you soon, god willing.
God willing.
Shira.
Y-Yoni, I don't feel good.
Sorry...
What's this? I know you.
I was with you at the base in Glilot.
Why are you here, what are you doing here?
Sorry... I don't understand what you're saying.
No, you understand, you understand.
Please, help me, what are you doing here?
What are we doing in Iran?
Sir, this woman is bothering me.
I don't know what she wants from me.
I apologize, miss.
How are you, Jila?
Okay.
Israel - Mossad
So the systems of the Jordanian plane are still under our control?
Excellent. Keep me updated.
Wait a minute, wait a second.
It's a call from the airport in Tehran.
Praise God
The weather's good here this morning. Very bright and sunny.
The passenger lied, we'll only get the codes
upon landing in Delhi.
That means we have a four hour delay.
We don't have four hours. The pilots will already be at the briefing by then.
There are other ways to get the codes.
I believe that Tamar can handle it.
This is exactly what we sent the hacker for.
What about the two Israelis?
Detained for questioning.
They bought tickets at the last minute and boarded the plane.
We only heard about it fifteen before take off.
Mike.
I want a full profile on both of them.
In the bathroom I saw an officer from my base.
Have you lost your mind?
I'm telling you, Yoni, I know her.
On Independence Day she became an Officer.
She's so beautiful, I've seen her a million times before.
A million times..
-Alright, enough, sshh. I don't want to hear it.
Yoni, listen for a second...
-Enough, no!
What do you think they'll do to us?
I don't know.
What?
I don't know, Yoni. Enough.
I knew it.
I knew we shouldn't have got on the flight.
Wait a second...
How beautiful.
What?
What's "what"?
You don't stop worrying even for a moment.
Everything's fine, darling. It'll all work out.
Me?
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about the price of the necklace you're looking at.
Do you want it?
Not anymore.
Try it on.
It's fine.
No...
Sorry, I need to answer this.
Try it on.
I'll be over here. It'll take two minutes.
Yes, Ali.
Hello commander. How are you?
Sorry to interrupt you. I know that you're at the airport.
What's the story? Get to the point.
A flight from Jordan landed an emergency landing with us.
There were two Israelis on board, they were taken to the special wing.
We're already on our way there.
No, there's no need to come.
It's not your job.
Yes sir.
I'm handling it. Ok? Ok.
Anything else I can help you with?
Well?
Very nice.
What's happening? Who was that?
Nothing, it was Ali. I..
I need to go do something in the field.
Something quick. I'll be back in time for the flight. Alright?
And if I tell you no?
Okay, you. We'll meet at the gate.
Right. I'll be back soon.
Okay, you.
So what do you think about the nuclear deal?
Who needs bombs when the value of our money loses a quarter of its worth every day?
Right.
I earn more every month but it's worth half what it was worth the previous month.
But the people at the top don't care if we live or die.
Where are you from? Where did you grow up?
I grew up in Tehran.
Where?
In "Garden".
Oh, what a neighborhood...
I have family there, the Azizi family.
We had neighbors by that name.
Really? Well, it's a large clan...
The family of Hudadad.
Their son was on the football team.
Nah, not them. Different family.
Sorry to say, but you have a slight accent.
My father was a merchant, and we travelled a lot.
Eventually we settled in Qatar.
Hey! Good for you!
What's happening here?
Hanging someone.
What did he do?
He was a bank manager.
Embezzled a bunch of oil money.
Please, take this.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks.
Keep it, it's fine.
I can't believe people come to watch this horror.
Is that her?
Put it on speaker.
Hello.
Good afternoon.
Peace to you.
How's the weather?
Bright.
Nice, nice.
You've arrived at the house?
Yes.
And the man is there?
Yes, he's a little stressed.
Do you think the Israeli girl at the airport noticed the switch?
I don't think so, she...
Honestly she was hysterical, they took her for questioning.
Are we going forward?
Jila didn't give us the codes.
Do you have a way around them?
I'll have to check...
There's a way. Yes, there's a way.
How?
I have somebody, some Iranian hacker that I know.
Who's that?
Someone who won't ask questions. He..
He'll want money.
OK, great. Keep me updated.
What's happening?
Are you ready for her break-in?
Yes sir.
In a moment we'll have a connection to the Iranian air force base,
she just needs to activate it for us.
And from here I'll be able to control the Iranian radar around the reactor.
It will see what I want it to see.
How much of a window are you giving the pilots?
They'll have about five minutes without anti-aircraft fire.
Separate them.
-Yes, commander.
Take it.
Hello
The gate is closing in 20 minutes. Are you coming?
I'll be there in two minutes.
Get them to hold. Tell them who I am and that there's a security issue.
I'll be right there.
It won't matter who you are. 300 people want to fly!
I'll be there in two minutes.
Thank you.
Here's the transcript of their conversation, sir.
OK. Thank you.
What a dick.
Ladies and gentlemen, the problem with the plane's computer has been fixed.
We are starting the boarding, please go to the gate. Thank you.
Yes, Faraz.
Sir.
I'm at the airport about the two Israelis.
Yes, I was informed.
The girl thinks she saw an Israeli intelligence officer
in an Iranian flight attendant's uniform.
Does that sound right to you?
I don't know.
The Israeli, does she seem credible to you?
There's no reason for her to lie about such a thing.
And assuming she's right, do you think she has a role in it?
She ran into her by mistake.
But if it were up to me, I would hold her over night at least.
Maybe she'll remember something else.
Well.
I feel it will do us more harm than good.
We don't need an international incident right now.
Release them. Let them board their connecting flight.
You're going with your wife to Paris, no?
Yes.
Go be with your wife and let Ali take care of it.
Good luck.
I'll pray for her.
Thank you.
Saeed.
I need footage from the camera covering the women's bathroom
from the moment the plane landed. It's urgent.
Yes, commander.
-Where is it?
Wait. Stop.
Go back, go back.
Wait.
Play it.
Look. Here she holds it in her left hand and here in her right.
Yes, boss.
Here, when she came in.
And here, six and a half minutes later, when she left.
It may not be the same girl.
I think this is the same person.
Zoom in.
These are two different women.
They switched.
Don't let the plane take off! No matter what!
Yes, commander.
Where's your bag?
Naahid...
That it? Are you done?
No.
Something serious came up. Very serious.
I must stay.
Ma'am, ma'am...
We have to close the gate, the plane is waiting.
Alright. Just one minute, please.
I have to stay.
Forgive me.
I'll catch the first plane tomorrow.
I took care of everything.
I'll be with you the entire time.
You'll get the Queen's treatment. I promise.
I'll join you tomorrow or the day after.
Sshh...
I'm tired of your empty promises.
How beautiful.
It looks so nice on you.
God is watching over us.
You'll get through this, darling.
With God's help.
Hurry, please.
Sorry.
-Thank you.
Safe trip.
-Thanks.
Well?
Sorry boss, there were orders from above to release the plane.
They took off.
We just received confirmation that the plane took off.
Two Israelis on board, plus Ashraf and the new passenger.
May God help you.
-You as well.
I see you finally got the surgery.
About time! Did you use the surgeon I recommended?
Yes.
Nice, I'm sure he did a great job.
What, going to work already? At this hour?
Well, you have a good evening, my dear.
-Good evening.
Iran - National Electric Company
Nice! You did the surgery?
When do the bandages come off so we can see?
In a few days.
Are you mad at me?
He's abusing you, Jila.
And you're not the first.
Someone needs to put him in his place.
If you don't, I will.
He's here.
Got called in for some problem.
He's on edge, be careful.
Our agent inside has 40 minutes to pull this off.
Counter.
The pilots are ready to go.
Switch to propulsion mode.
Choshen 1 through 4, you may align on 8-1.
Choshen 1 through 4, ready and waiting on 8-1.
We have a ping from Tehran.
OK, she managed to get in through the backdoor
of the IEC backup system for the Air Force.
She's started accessing the equipment.
I was told that you were here.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Wait, what happened?
I don't understand what's happening, she's not responding.
Come here.
Jila, wait!
Darling!
There's no response.
What's wrong, you slut?
-Hey!
Your husband found out, and now you're upset?
Don't fight.
Come on, darling.
Come on, take my cock.
What's this? Who are you?
Previews not subtitled.